Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - A
        - Atkins - We gon' make you feel good; Easy street, 1982; SR-10940; Atkins (Box 176)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1047; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-1047-SH1
        - Atkins, Juan - Coke Dj-culture Remix By Juan Atkins / Blake Baxter, 2005; SR-10941; Atkins, Juan; Baxter, Blake (Box 176)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # 57644 1A CC 08V
          Coke Dj-culture
        - Sweet Pea Atkinson - Don't walk away, 1982; SR-10942; Sweet Pea Atkinson (Box 176)
          Catalog # 90007-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL-824981-A
        - ATL - Make it up with love, 2004; SR-10943; ATL (Box 176)
          Catalog # EAS 58322; A-side Matrix # XSS-58322-A
        - ATL - Calling all girls, 2003; SR-10944; ATL (Box 176)
          Catalog # EAS 59693; A-side Matrix # XSS-59693A-1A
        - Atlantic Starr - (Let's) rock and roll, 1979; SR-10945; Atlantic Starr (Box 176)
          Catalog # SP-17079; A-side Matrix # A&M SP17141S-ME
        - Atlantic Starr - Secret lovers… the best of Atlantic Starr, 1986; SR-10946; Atlantic Starr (Box 176)
          Catalog # SP-5141; A-side Matrix # SP-05141-A ES-1
        - Atlantic Starr - One lover at a time, 1987; SR-10947; Atlantic Starr (Box 176)
          Catalog # 0-20699; A-side Matrix # 0-20699-A SH-1
        - Atlantic Starr - Kissin' power, 1978; SR-10948; Atlantic Starr (Box 176)
          Catalog # SP-12026; A-side Matrix # A&MSP12026A-S2
        - Atlantic Starr - Armed and dangerous, 1986; SR-10949; Atlantic Starr (Box 176)
          Catalog # V-56029; A-side Matrix # V-1-56029-241039B-Z2
        - Atlantic Starr - Secret lovers, 1985; SR-10950; Atlantic Starr (Box 176)
          Catalog # AMY 307; A-side Matrix # AMY 307 A
        - Atlantis - Keep on movin' and groovin', 1982; SR-10951; Atlantis (Box 176)
          Catalog # CHDS 2524; A-side Matrix # CHDS-2524-A-RE
          Chaz Ro
        - Atlas, Natacha - Yalla chant, 1995; SR-10952; Atlas, Natacha (Box 176)
          Catalog # NAT 60T; A-side Matrix # NAT 60-A
          Nation Records
        - Atmosfear - Xtra special, 1982; SR-10953; Atmosfear (Box 176)
          Catalog # ICS 111; A-side Matrix # ICS-111-A
          City Sounds
        - Atmospherix - What I need, 2000; SR-10954; Atmospherix; DJ ATX (Box 176)
          Catalog # BBR 005; A-side Matrix # BBR 005-A
          Big Bang Records
          West Newton, Massachusetts
        - Atmospheric - Admit it; Speak and spell, 1989; SR-10955; Atmospheric (Box 176)
          Catalog # PRO-7253; A-side Matrix # PRO-7253-A
        - Atomic Hooligan - Dreams of life, 2002; SR-10956; Atomic Hooligan (Box 176)
          Catalog # 2S2007; A-side Matrix # 08 49929 20 1A1 2S2 007
          2S2
        - Attitude - We got the juice, 1983; SR-10957; Attitude (Box 176)
          In same jacket as # SR-10958. 2 copies
          Catalog # DMD 601; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-44047-44048-1
        - Attitude - We got the juice, 1983; SR-10958; Attitude (Box 176)
          In same jacket as # SR-10957. 2 copies
        - Jean-Louis Aubert'n'Ko - Plâtre et ciment !, 1987; SR-10959; Jean-Louis Aubert'n'Ko (Box 176)
          In same jacket as # SR-10960. 2 copies
          Catalog # 70485; A-side Matrix # M6 355 587 2
        - Jean-Louis Aubert'n'Ko - Plâtre et ciment !, 1987; SR-10960; Jean-Louis Aubert'n'Ko (Box 176)
          In same jacket as # SR-10959. 2 copies
        - Audio Two - Top billin', 1988; SR-10961; Audio Two (Box 176)
          Catalog # PR 4516; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-62423-62424-1
          First Priority Music
        - Audio Two - Many styles; The questions, 1988; SR-10962; Audio Two (Box 176)
          Catalog # 0-96585; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-56390-56391-1
        - Audio Two - Hickeys around my neck, 1988; SR-10963; Audio Two (Box 176)
          Catalog # DMD 1228; A-side Matrix # STDM-55395-55696-55697-1
        - Aural Exciters - Chinese rap, 1982; SR-10964; Aural Exciters (Box 176)
          Catalog # TOP-002; A-side Matrix # TOP-002A-RE
          Top Flight Records
        - Aural Exciters - My boy lollipop, 1979; SR-10965; Aural Exciters (Box 176)
          Catalog # ZEA 12-005; A-side Matrix # ZEA-12005 AS-1D
          ZE Records
        - Aural Exciters - Spooks in space, 1979; SR-10966; Aural Exciters (Box 176)
          Catalog # ZEA 12-002; A-side Matrix # ZEA-12-0025A-7
        - Aurra - A little love; In my arms, 1982; SR-10967; Aurra (Box 176)
          Catalog # SG 366; A-side Matrix # SG-366-A
        - Aurra - Keep doin' it; Nasty disposition, 1981; SR-10968; Aurra (Box 176)
          Catalog # SG 352; A-side Matrix # SG-352-A-1
        - Aurra - Make up your mind, 1981; SR-10969; Aurra (Box 176)
          Catalog # SG 360; A-side Matrix # SG-360-A
        - Aurra - Are you single; Living too fast, 1981; SR-10970; Aurra (Box 176)
          Catalog # SG 346; A-side Matrix # SG-346-A-1
        - Aurra - Checking you out, 1982; SR-10971; Aurra (Box 176)
          Catalog # SG 369; A-side Matrix # SG-369-A
        - Aurra - Aurra, 1980; SR-10972; Aurra (Box 176)
          Catalog # DA 3503; A-side Matrix # DA-3503-A
          Dream Records
        - Aurra - Live and let live, 1983; SR-10973; Aurra (Box 176)
          Catalog # SA 8559; A-side Matrix # SA-8559-A
        - Austin, Patti - The heat of heat, 1985; SR-10974; Austin, Patti (Box 176)
          Catalog # 0-20462; A-side Matrix # 0-20462-A-SH1
          Qwest Records
        - Austin, Patti - The heat of heat, 1985; SR-10975; Austin, Patti (Box 176)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2339; A-side Matrix # PRO A1 2339 SH1
        - Austin, Patti - Do you love me?, 1981; SR-10976; Austin, Patti (Box 176)
          Catalog # PRO-A-967; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-967-S-RE-1 A1
        - Automator - Music to be murdered by, 1989; SR-10977; Automator (Box 176)
          Catalog # Hb88265; A-side Matrix # hb-88365-1
          HomeBass Records
          Berkeley, California
        - AUX 88 - Break it down; The countdown, 1996; SR-10978; AUX 88 (Box 176)
          Catalog # DB4W-019; A-side Matrix # DB4W-019A
          Direct Beat
          Detroit, Michigan
        - AUX 88 - Is it man or machine (Disc one), 1996; SR-10979; AUX 88 (Box 176)
          In same jacket as # SR-10980. Double album
          Catalog # DB4W-022; A-side Matrix # DBW-022 S1
        - AUX 88 - Is it man or machine (Disc two), 1996; SR-10980; AUX 88 (Box 176)
          In same jacket as # SR-10979. Double album
          Catalog # DB4W-022; A-side Matrix # DBW-022 S3
        - Avalon, Frankie - You’re the miracle, 1983; SR-10981; Avalon, Frankie (Box 176)
          Catalog # AS 1716; A-side Matrix # XSM 171312-1F
          Bobcat Records
        - Avant - Separated, 2000; SR-10982; Avant (Box 176)
          Catalog # MCAR 25024-1; A-side Matrix # MCA 13678
        - Avant - Makin' good love, 2001; SR-10983; Avant (Box 176)
          Catalog # MCAR-25618-1; A-side Matrix # MCAR-256181-A RE1
        - Avant - 4 minutes, 2006; SR-10984; Avant (Box 176)
          In same jacket as # SR-10985. 2 copies
          Catalog # GEFR115711; A-side Matrix # GEFR 11571-1 A
        - Avant - 4 minutes, 2006; SR-10985; Avant (Box 176)
          In same jacket as # SR-10984. 2 copies
        - Average Crowd - Straight ahead nonstop, 1990; SR-10986; Average Crowd (Box 176)
          Catalog # MR 008; A-side Matrix # MR 008 A
          Merge Records
          Plainfield, New Jersey
        - Average White Band - Volume VIII, 1980; SR-10987; Average White Band (Box 177)
          Catalog # ST-A-804445; A-side Matrix # ST-A-804445-C
        - Average White Band - Put it where you want it, 1973; SR-10988; Average White Band (Box 177)
          Catalog # MCA-475; A-side Matrix # MCA 643-W1
        - Avitabile, Enzo - Punta il naso a nord, 1988; SR-10989; Avitabile, Enzo (Box 177)
          Catalog # 14 2027596; A-side Matrix # 2027596-A-13-6-88
          Costa Est
        - Avitabile, Enzo - Alta tensione, 1988; SR-10990; Avitabile, Enzo (Box 177)
          Catalog # 14 2028846; A-side Matrix # 2028846-A 14-9-88I
        - Avitabile, Enzo - Meglio soul, 1983; SR-10991; Avitabile, Enzo (Box 177)
          Catalog # 64 1186261; A-side Matrix # 1186261-A 28-7-83
          EMI
        - Avitabile, Enzo - Alta tensione, 1988; SR-10992; Avitabile, Enzo (Box 177)
          Catalog # 64 7906381; A-side Matrix # 7906381-A-5-5-88
        - Avonn - Everybody get down, 1981; SR-10993; Avonn (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-10994. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # RB-1001; A-side Matrix # RB-1001-A
          RBL Records and Tapes
        - Avonn - Everybody get down, 1981; SR-10994; Avonn (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-10993. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Avril - The date (dated girls remix), 2002; SR-10995; Avril (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-10996. Different discs
          Catalog # F163W; A-side Matrix # B266215-01 A1
        - Avril - French kiss, 2001; SR-10996; Avril (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-10995. Different discs
          Catalog # F156W; A-side Matrix # B158100-01 A1
        - Aw-Sum - This love is right, 1987; SR-10997; Aw-Sum (Box 177)
          Catalog # SRU-80587; A-side Matrix # SRU 80587-A
          Strawberry Records Unltd.
          Mt Vernon, New York
        - Awesome Dre' - Frankly speaking; Executioner style, 1989; SR-10998; Awesome Dre'; Hardcore Committee (Box 177)
          Catalog # PVL07274; A-side Matrix # VL-1-7211-21
        - Awesome Dre' - A.D.'s revenge, 1993; SR-10999; Awesome Dre'; Hardcore Committee (Box 177)
          Catalog # 97103-1; A-side Matrix # SRRAD93 A
          Strictly Roots Recordings
        - Axx of Jahpostles - Give thanks and praise, 1996; SR-11000; Axx of Jahpostles (Box 177)
          Catalog # AXX 0001; A-side Matrix # GIVE THANKS AND PRAISE
          Axx Production
          Jamaica
        - Ayers, Roy - Nasté, 1995; SR-11001; Ayers, Roy (Box 177)
          Catalog # RDAB 64361; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64361-1-A-1
          Groovetown
        - Ayers, Roy - Stoned soul picnic, 1968; SR-11002; Ayers, Roy (Box 177)
          Catalog # SD 1514; A-side Matrix # ST-A-681375-A
        - Ayers, Roy - Freaky deaky, 1978; SR-11003; Ayers, Roy (Box 177)
          Catalog # PRO 037; A-side Matrix # PRO 037 77NP
        - Ayers, Roy - Love fantasy, 1980; SR-11004; Ayers, Roy (Box 177)
          Catalog # PD-1-6301; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6301-AS-PW
        - Ayers, Roy - Slip n' slide, 1985; SR-11005; Ayers, Roy (Box 177)
          Catalog # CAS 2175; A-side Matrix # XSS-174617-1A
        - Ayers, Roy - Love will bring us back together, 1979; SR-11006; Ayers, Roy (Box 177)
          Catalog # PRO 093; A-side Matrix # PRO 093 79NP 4109 S9D1
        - Ayers, Roy - Don't stop the feeling, 1979; SR-11007; Ayers, Roy (Box 177)
          Catalog # PRO 119; A-side Matrix # PRO 11979NP 4560-SHORT-S-CP4
        - AZ - Doe or die, 1996; SR-11008; AZ (Box 177)
          Catalog # SPRO-10476; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10476-A
          EMI Records
        - AZ - Doe or die, 1995; SR-11009; AZ (Box 177)
          Catalog # E1-32631; A-side Matrix # E1-32631-A RE1
        - AZ - Gimme yours, 1995; SR-11010; AZ (Box 177)
          Catalog # SPRO-10451; A-side Matrix # Y-58512 ARE1
        - AZ - Doe or die, 1996; SR-11011; AZ (Box 177)
        - AZ - Sugar hill, 1995; SR-11012; AZ (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-11013. 2 copies
          Catalog # SPRO 10439; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10439-A
        - AZ - Sugar hill, 1995; SR-11013; AZ (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-11012. 2 copies
        - AZ - Gimme yours, 1995; SR-11014; AZ (Box 177)
          Catalog # Y-58512; A-side Matrix # Y-58512 A RE1
        - Azeem - Garage opera (Disc one), 2000; SR-11015; Azeem (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-11016. Double album
          Catalog # HTK010; A-side Matrix # HTK 010-A
          Heratik Productions
        - Azeem - Garage opera (Disc two), 2000; SR-11016; Azeem (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-11015. Double album
          Catalog # HTK010; A-side Matrix # HTK 010-C
        - Azucar Moreno - Bandido, 1990; SR-11017; Azucar Moreno (Box 177)
          Catalog # EPC 655860 6; A-side Matrix # EPC-655860-6 A
          Madrid, Spain
        - Azzido Da Bass - Dooms night, 1999; SR-11018; Azzido Da Bass (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-11019. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # 0122370CLU; A-side Matrix # B041261-01 A1 HL
          Club Tools
        - Azzido Da Bass - Dooms night, 1999; SR-11019; Azzido Da Bass (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-11018. 2 copies. Annotated
        - A+ - All I see remix, 1996; SR-13552; A+ (Box 177)
          Different jacket
          Catalog # U8P1064; A-side Matrix # U8P-1064A
        - Abyss - Catch 22 (Damn if you do damn if you don't), 2002; SR-15000; Abyss (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-15001. Different discs
          Catalog # PR 300590; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-90231-90232-1
        - Scritti Politti - Another sound mission (Mystic handyman Pt 2), 1999; SR-15001; Scritti Politti; Likwit Crew (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-15000. Different discs
          Catalog # 7087-6-14925-1-4; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7087-6-14925-1-4-A
        - AC/DC - Back in black, 1980; SR-15002; AC/DC (Box 177)
          Catalog # SD 16018; A-side Matrix # ST-A-804517-C
        - Sunny Ade & his Green Spot Band - The master guitarist Vol. 1, 1970; SR-15003; Sunny Ade & his Green Spot Band; Ade, Sunny (Box 177)
          Catalog # LPAS 8006; A-side Matrix # LPAS 8006B
          African Songs Ltd
        - Sunny Ade & his Green Spot Band - The master guitarist Vol. 2 in the heart of Great Britain, 1970; SR-15004; Sunny Ade & his Green Spot Band; Ade, Sunny (Box 177)
          Catalog # 2YEF 118; A-side Matrix # 2YEF 118-1
        - Admiral Tebet - Fancy girl; Nah get di glami, 1987; SR-15005; Admiral Tebet; Sister Charmaine (Box 177)
          Catalog # WR5527; A-side Matrix # WR-5527-A-Fancy girl
          Techniques
        - African Business - In Zaire business, 1990; SR-15006; African Business (Box 177)
          Catalog # URBX 64; A-side Matrix # URBX 64 A-1U-1-1
        - African Business - In Zaire business, 1990; SR-15007; African Business (Box 177)
        - Ahzz - New York's movin', 1981; SR-15008; Ahzz (Box 177)
          Catalog # 903-A; A-side Matrix # LH-903-A
          Land Of Hits
        - Al & The Kidd - Al & the kidd; The planet of love, 1979; SR-15009; Al & The Kidd (Box 177)
          Catalog # AK-1001; A-side Matrix # AK-1001
          Al & The Kidd Records
        - Aleem - Get down Friday night, 1982; SR-13787; Aleem; Fantastic Aleems; Burgess, Leroy (Box 177)
          Catalog # N-007; A-side Matrix # N-007-A
          Nia Records
        - Aleem - Movin' to the beat, 1981; SR-13788; Aleem; Fantastic Aleems; Hodges, Corky (Box 177)
          Catalog # N-035; A-side Matrix # N-035-A
        - Almighty Funketeers - In full force: funky live, 1986; SR-15010; Almighty Funketeers (Box 177)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # KTR/AMEB/FLOOIC1986/R1-A
          Kent Town Associates Records
          Landover Hills, Maryland
        - AM-FM - You are the one, 1981; SR-13703; AM-FM (Box 177)
          Catalog # DK 103; A-side Matrix # DK-103-A-1-1
          Dakar Records
          White Plains, New York
        - Anderson, Sunshine - Heard it all before (Dance remixes), 2001; SR-15011; Anderson, Sunshine (Box 177)
          Catalog # 0-95523; A-side Matrix # STDM-90217-90218-1
        - Andres, Pablo - La cucaracha; Vaquero estilo; Microclimat, 2002; SR-13827; Andres, Pablo (Box 177)
          Catalog # 131279-A1; A-side Matrix # 131279 A1
          Pablo Andres / Skinfama
        - Angel Witch - Angel witch, 1980; SR-15012; Angel Witch (Box 177)
          Catalog # BRON 532; A-side Matrix # BRON 532 A
          Bronze
        - Anges Pressés - Revoluzion, 1992; SR-13789; Anges Pressés (Box 177)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # LUV 001 A1
          Les Anges Pressés
        - Ann Margret - Love rush- e minor, 1979; SR-15013; Ann Margret (Box 177)
          Catalog # OR 7511; A-side Matrix # OR 7511 AS RE1-1B
          Ocean Ariola America
        - Anotha Level - Don't stimulate; What's that cha say; Fo sho shot; Doubt we ever quit, 1994; SR-15014; Anotha Level (Box 177)
          Catalog # SPRO 50805; A-side Matrix # SPRO 50805 A
        - Another Nasty Move - Two too the jaw, 1994; SR-15015; Another Nasty Move (Box 177)
          Catalog # ANM-1; A-side Matrix # ANM-1 A
          Nubian Productions Enterprises, Inc.
        - Aquarium Dream - Norman Connor presents, 1976; SR-15016; Aquarium Dream (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-15017. 2 copies
          Catalog # BDS 5672; A-side Matrix # BDS-5672A-1A
          Buddah Records
        - Aquarium Dream - Norman Connor presents, 1976; SR-15017; Aquarium Dream (Box 177)
          In same jacket as # SR-15016. 2 copies
          Catalog # BDS 5672; A-side Matrix # BDS-5672A-
        - Aragorn Ballroom Orchestra - (Theme from) The lord of the rings, 1978; SR-15018; Aragorn Ballroom Orchestra (Box 226)
          Catalog # D-119; A-side Matrix # D-119-A
          Fantasy Records
        - Arrow - Classics plus, 1994; SR-15019; Arrow (Box 226)
          Catalog # ARROW 042; A-side Matrix # ARROW-042-A
          Arrow Music Ltd.
        - Arrow - Hot hot hot "Universal dance mixes '94", 1994; SR-15020; Arrow (Box 226)
          Catalog # ARROW 041; A-side Matrix # ARROW 041-A
        - Asher D - Ragamuffin hip hop, 1987; SR-15021; Asher D; Daddy Freddy (Box 226)
          Catalog # NOTE 5; A-side Matrix # NOTE-5-A
          Music of Life
          Denmark
        - Atila - International Sandwich, 1981; SR-15022; Atila (Box 226)
          Catalog # FR1000; A-side Matrix # S-10341-
          Fish Ranch Records
        - Aufnahme - Ein, zwei, drei, vier, 1988; SR-15023; Aufnahme (Box 226)
          In same jacket as # SR-15024. 2 copies
          Catalog # MEET 041; A-side Matrix # MEET 041 A
          Meet Records
        - Aufnahme - Ein, zwei, drei, vier, 1988; SR-15024; Aufnahme (Box 226)
          In same jacket as # SR-15023. 2 copies
        - AV8 - Where my dawgs @?!!, 2000; SR-15025; AV8 (Box 226)
          Catalog # AV-110; A-side Matrix # AV-110-A
          AV8
        - Average White Band - Person to person (Disc one), 1976; SR-15026; Average White Band (Box 226)
          In same jacket as # SR-15027; SR-15028; SR-15029. Double album;. 2 copies
          Catalog # SD2-1002; A-side Matrix # ST-A-763759-D
        - Average White Band - Person to person (Disc two), 1976; SR-15027; Average White Band (Box 226)
          In same jacket as # SR-15026; SR-15028; SR-15029. Double album;. 2 copies
          Catalog # SD2-1002; A-side Matrix # ST-A-763761-D
        - Average White Band - Person to person (Disc one), 1976; SR-15028; Average White Band (Box 226)
          In same jacket as # SR-15026; SR-15027; SR-15029. Double album;. 2 copies
        - Average White Band - Person to person (Disc two), 1976; SR-15029; Average White Band (Box 226)
          In same jacket as # SR-15026; SR-15027; SR-15028. Double album;. 2 copies
        - Amalgamation of Soundz - Theory EP, 1996; SR-17644; Amalgamation of Soundz (Box 226)
          Catalog # FILT 0011; A-side Matrix # FILT-011-A1
          Filter
        - Andall, Ella - Hello Africa, 1976; SR-17645; Andall, Ella; Shorty Vibration International (Box 226)
          Catalog # S-017; A-side Matrix # S017-A-D
          Shorty
          Trinidad & Tobago
        - Aphrodite - Ganja man; Heat haze, 2002; SR-17646; Aphrodite (Box 226)
          Catalog # APH-42A; A-side Matrix # APH 42A
        - Arsonists - Blacklisted; MC squared, 1999; SR-17647; Arsonists; Anomolies; Battalion (Box 226)
          Catalog # SUB 777; A-side Matrix # 25-SUB-777-1 A
          Sub Records
        - Assassin - Remix volume 3, Date Unknown; SR-17648; Assassin; DJ Fashion; Busta Rhymes; Elephant Man (Box 226)
          Catalog # CR003R; A-side Matrix # CR-003R-A
          Callaloo Records
        - Aswad - Warrior charge; Dub charge, 1980; SR-17649; Aswad; Gordon, Vin; Rose, Michael 'Bami' (Box 226)
          Catalog # 12WIP 6646; A-side Matrix # 12WTP 6646 A-TU
          Grove Music
        - Adventures of Stevie V. - Jealousy, 1990; SR-25144; Adventures of Stevie V. (Box 252)
          Catalog # 878 663-1; A-side Matrix # 878-663-1-A
        - Aerosmith - Toys in the attic, 1975; SR-25145; Aerosmith (Box 252)
          In same jacket as # SR-25146; SR-25147. 2 copies
          Catalog # JC 33479; A-side Matrix # PAL 33479 1C L.S.J.D.
          Columbia
        - Aerosmith - Toys in the attic, 1975; SR-25146; Aerosmith (Box 252)
          In same jacket as # SR-25145; SR-25147. 2 copies
        - Dibango, Manu - Makossa man, 1973; SR-25147; Dibango, Manu (Box 252)
          In same jacket as # SR-25145; SR-25146. Different discs
          Catalog # SD 7276; A-side Matrix # STA733013A
        - AG - Rude awakening, 1999; SR-25148; AG (Box 252)
          Catalog # AG8889; A-side Matrix # AG 8888 A
          Silva Dom Records
        - Amazulu - Smiley stylee, 1983; SR-25149; Amazulu (Box 252)
          Catalog # 12 TOW 40; A-side Matrix # 12 TOW 40 A
          Towerbell Records
        - Ambassadeurs - The best of Ambassadeurs, 1984; SR-25150; Ambassadeurs (Box 252)
          Catalog # CEL 6640; A-side Matrix # Cel 6640A
        - Ant Dub - Picture this, 2004; SR-25151; Ant Dub (Box 252)
          Catalog # CTX 494; A-side Matrix # CTX-494-A
          Trax Records
        - Anthony, Mike - Why can't we live together, 1982; SR-25152; Anthony, Mike (Box 252)
          Catalog # SUN 403; A-side Matrix # SUN-403-A
          Sunnyview
        - Aphrodite - Project 2, 2000; SR-25153; Aphrodite (Box 252)
          Catalog # APH33; A-side Matrix # APH 33-A
        - Aristakes - Diamond is forever! (Neil's diamonds), 1981; SR-25154; Aristakes (Box 252)
          Catalog # ICS 110; A-side Matrix # ICS-110-A
        - Army Of Lovers - Obsession, 1991; SR-25155; Army Of Lovers (Box 252)
          Catalog # WOKT 2009; A-side Matrix # WOKT 2009 A1
          Ton Son Ton
        - Ashford, Jack - Hotel sheet, 1977; SR-25156; Ashford, Jack (Box 252)
          Catalog # MD-116; A-side Matrix # MD 116-A RE-1 S-5337 P.B.
          Magic Disc Records
        - Erna morena - Association P.C., 1973; SR-25157; Erna morena (Box 252)
          Catalog # MB 21542; A-side Matrix # MB-21542 A-1
          MPS Records
          Bedford, Massachusetts
        - Autotune - Ladyshaker (Disc one), 2000; SR-25158; Autotune (Box 252)
          In same jacket as # SR-25159. Double album
          Catalog # Müller 2024; A-side Matrix # Müller 2024 A
          Müller Records
        - Autotune - Ladyshaker (Disc two), 2000; SR-25159; Autotune (Box 252)
          In same jacket as # SR-25158. Double album
          Catalog # Müller 2024; A-side Matrix # Müller 2024 C